illusionmage.com 2013-03-28

# Privacy Policy For IllusionMage

I. This notice is to inform you about the policies for collection and use of personally identifiable information on the IllusionMage.com site. Sites which are linked to our site may have different policies; please review the privacy policy notices on those sites for details. 

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you on this site without your knowledge, and all such information is collected directly from you. For example, we may ask you to provide your e-mail address, name, mailing address, or other information about yourself in order to participate in contests, chat rooms, or on bulletin boards, to be added to the list to receive e-mail updates on particular artists or types of music, to send so-called "postcards" or to conduct transactions at The Store or elsewhere on the site. You are not required to provide us with this information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to participate in some of the activities on this site. We do not use cookies on this site but our advertisers, sponsors, payment processor and tracking counters may. 

We use the information we collect from you to allow you to participate in the site activities for which the information is collected. For example, when you give us your e-mail address in order to receive updates, that address is added to the e-mail list for that area. On each e-mail you receive, you are given the opportunity to unsubscribe; when you unsubscribe, we remove your e-mail address permanently from that mailing list. 

For contests conducted on this site, we use the personal information you provide only for the purpose of contacting you if you win a prize and sending the prize to you. We do not use contact information contained in contest entries to create mailing lists or for any other purpose. For further information about how we handle entries to a particular contest, please consult the contest rules. 

We do not share personal information provided by site visitors with anyone outside IllusionMage.com, except to the extent necessary to allow you to participate in site activities (for example, to send you a prize that you have won in a contest on the site). In particular, we do not rent or sell mailing lists of site visitors to any third party. 

We try to keep the information we collect from you as current as possible, and we take steps to maintain the security of your personal information and to prevent unauthorized access to it by those who do not have a legitimate need for it. We will never post your e-mail address or other identifying information you have provided on our site without your consent. 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that FlightProSim or it affiliated companies is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

This website takes certain precautions to protect our users' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. However, there is unfortunately no way yet for the industry to guarantee that the information you transmit through the Internet is entirely secure. 

Users are responsible for securing the confidentiality of their password and account, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under their password or account. It is strongly recommended that users take extra precautions when receiving files from unfamiliar third parties (i.e., via email), as they may be harmful. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If you reject the cookie, you may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that you will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, you may not be able to participate in some of our Sweepstakes, Contests or monthly Drawings that may take place. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we may share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 

These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you provided to us. This can be done by sending us an [e-mail ](http://www.illusionmage.com/support). 

This website is not specifically directed at or intended for children. Our public forums, such as the chat rooms and message boards, are considered non-confidential communications. Much of the content in these public areas, including the content within specific messages, comments or postings is provided by and is the responsibility of the third party creator of the communication or the person posting the information. FlightProSim does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any public forum and, therefore, FlightProSim specifically disclaims any liability with regard to public forums and any actions resulting from a user's participation in any public forum. FlightProSim has no responsibility for such content and is merely providing access to such content as a service to its users. 

**II. INFORMATION PRACTICES WITH REGARD TO CHILDREN**

If you are under 13 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information on this site without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. If we learn that you are under 13 years of age, we will not maintain or use any personally identifiable information about you without the verifiable consent of your parent or guardian, except as allowed by law. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the site without that verifiable consent. 

We collect personally identifiable information directly from visitors on this site who may be under the age of 13. We do not collect this information without the knowledge of the visitor. 

Our activities on this site are carried out in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. Under that Act, we may not ask a child to provide more personal information than is reasonably necessary in order to participate in an activity on this site. We comply with this requirement, and any personally identifiable information collected from a visitor on this site is used only for the purpose of enabling the visitor's participation in activities on this site. 

For example, we ask visitors who wish to be placed on a specific mailing list for a newsletter to provide an e-mail address. This information is used to send the visitor the newsletter requested. We also ask visitors who wish to receive a free promotional item (such as a CD, t-shirt, etc.) to provide name, mailing address, and e-mail address. The name and mailing address are used to send the visitor the promotional item. The e-mail address is used only if we need to contact the visitor to verify name and mailing address. We do not retain this information after the item has been delivered, and we do not use it for any other purpose. 

For contests that are held on this site, we ask each contestant to provide year of birth, as well as name, address, and e-mail address. If the year provided indicates that the contestant may not be at least 13 years old, the information submitted is deleted. Information submitted in order to participate in a contest is not used for any other purpose. Please refer to the specific age requirements for each contest as rules may vary from contest to contest. 

We ask each visitor who wishes to participate in chat rooms and bulletin boards on this site to provide an e-mail address along with the visitor's screen name. Each visitor who wishes to send a so-called "postcard" is asked to provide the visitor's screen name and e-mail address, the recipient's name and e-mail address, and a message selected by the visitor. All such e-mail addresses are used only to protect the security and integrity of the site, such as to take action against visitors who post inappropriate material or harass other visitors. 

Some of the activities on our site (e.g., certain chat rooms and bulletin boards), require participants to be 13 years of age or older. When you sign up for any of these activities, we will ask you to enter your date of birth. This information will not be used, stored, or published for any purposes other than to ensure the compliance of such age restrictions with respect to those age restricted activities. 

In some circumstances, we also ask visitors to this site to provide us with contact information on their parent or guardian. We use this information only for the purpose of contacting the parent or guardian to notify them of our information practices with respect to children, to notify that person of a child's participation on this site, and/or to seek the consent of the parent or guardian to such participation. 

The parent or guardian of any person under the age of 13 whose personal information we have collected on this site may ask to review that personal information, to have it deleted, and to forbid further collection of the information. For more information on how to do this, please contact the contact person listed below. 

No personal information collected on this site is shared with third parties other than a parent or guardian of a site visitor, except that information may be shared with those with whom we contract to carry out the internal operations of the site (for example, to send you a promotional item that you have requested on the site.). These contractors have agreed with us to use personal information of site visitors only for the purposes of carrying out these operations. In particular, we do not rent or sell mailing lists of site visitors to any third party. 

If you have questions concerning this policy please feel free to contact us through our site. [Contact ](http://www.illusionmage.com/support)[ Us Here ](http://illusionmage.com/support/)

Queries can also be sent to our physical address at:

Customer Services  
PO Box 20420  
Highbrook   
Auckland 2161   
New Zealand 

This document may change as our site develops and grows, so please re-visit this page as often as you wish. 

Please note changes to the privacy policy , disclaimers or terms and conditions  take effect immeditaly upon posting / become live on this site. Any further use of this website and the content encolsed within by yourself or someone under your direct care/supervision, indicates you have read and accept these complete documents.
